Some of you are taking the side of terrorists and it's disgusting. I don't understand it.
Don't worry bro, I got you. I recommend therapy twice a week for about a year just for starters.
And two, if we are supporting terrorism then you must also recognize that the Red Cross, Doctors Without Borders, Amnesty International, Human Rights Watch, UNICEF, the government of South Africa, the Maldives, the South American continent, Africa, island nations, basically anyone who is not Western Europe and North America are all terrorist supporters.
Because you see this rage that you have inside you that you don't understand and it affects every aspect of your life, that's called aggrieved white nationalism.
And you're so pissed all the time because it requires that you exist in a state of cognitive dissonance and hypocrisy.
You want your freedom, you want your guns, and your don't tread on me flags, low taxes, the right to resist a government that won't stay out of your business or your church.
We hold these truths to be self-evident that all men are created equal, 4th of July, Declaration of Independence baby.
And here's the dissonance. The second that someone who doesn't look like us wants the same thing, it's a threat.
If he's black, he's a criminal. If he's brown, he's a terrorist. If he's Hispanic, he's an illegal immigrant.
If he's Asian, he's a communist.
But you support Israel unconditionally because it allows you to tell yourself you ain't racist.
But anti-Semitism, while very real and abhorrent, is not the status quo. Islamophobia is the status quo.
It says Muslims are prone to terrorism and radicalization so we can just bomb the shit out of them.
But that's not true because human beings are overwhelmingly peaceful.
They just want security, basic human rights and dignity, and to provide for their families.
It takes a lot of propaganda to get the common people to call for war.
You've clearly been gobbling up that post-9-11 shit with relish.
It's also fascinating to me that the people who have been never touched by violence turn out to be the biggest war pigs.
And just because you own guns doesn't mean you know anything of violence.
And one last thing, since you like to do ad hominem attacks on people who don't like genocide,
I'll say that as a Texan and a former U.S. Army Ranger, your gun slinging is trash.
And you really should be training with multiple targets so you can hone your acquisition skills,
but actually, don't do that. Continue to suck.
I can't believe you posted this. Big yikes.